ILGWU. Wilbur Daniels papers, 5780/084
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. General/Administrative, 1937-1985
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    6 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    7 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    8 of 9
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; memos, meeting materials, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    9 of 9
  - National Commission on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    September 22; 1 of 2
  - National Commission on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    September 22; 2 of 2
  - National Commission on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    September 23; 1 of 2
  - National Commission on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    September 23; 2 of 2
  - National Commission on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    September 24
  - ILGWU. Wilbur Daniels papers, 1937-1987. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Public Assistance and Unemployment Compensation, Hearings, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    August 10; 1 of 2
  - Subcommittee on Public Assistance and Unemployment Compensation, Hearings, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    August 10; 2 of 2
  - National Committee on Unemployment Compensation; Meeting Transcript, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    August 30
  - Statements, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Statements, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Briefing Book: House Hearing on Cost Equalization, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Testimony, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Our "UC Story (Box 35, Folder 8)
    by Paul Raushenbush and Elizabeth Brandeis Raushenbush
  - Printed Material, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Printed Material, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    2 of 4
  - Printed Material, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Printed Material, 1973-1979 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - [Wilbur Daniels retirement], 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Local 62-32, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Maidenform, 1974-1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Maidenform, 1974-1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Delegate Kits, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Convention Memos, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Guests: Convention, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Security: Convention, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Slogans: Convention, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Speakers: Convention, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series IV. Master Agreements Department, 1949-1980
  This series contains: Agreements, Arbitration Cases, Bargaining Demands, Clippings, Correspondence, Constitution Clauses, Contract Clauses, Legal Documents, Mediation Notices, Miscellaneous Photographs, Negotiations, Notes, Settlements, Wage Standards
  - General. A (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Undated. Apparel Manufacturing; Apparel New England Corporation; Avalon Classics, Inc.
  - Associated Corset and Brassiere. General. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Associated Corset and Brassiere. General. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Associated Corset and Brassiere. General. [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - General. B, 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Beeline Fashions; Brooks Transportation Inc.; Brownsville Manufacturing Company
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 1 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 2 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 3 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 4 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 5 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Barbizon Corporation. General. [folder 6 of 6], 1965-1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Barbizon Corporation. Master Agreements, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Barbizon Corporation. Negotiations and Agreements. [folder 1 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Barbizon Corporation. Negotiations and Agreements. [folder 2 of 2], 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Barbizon Corporation. Paterson Arbitration, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Barbizon Corporation. Supplemental Agreements, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. General. [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. General. [folder 2 of 5], 1964-1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. General. [folder 3 of 5], 1964-1978 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. General. [folder 4 of 5], 1964-1978 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. General. [folder 5 of 5], 1964-1978 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1977 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. Supplemental Agreements, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Aletta Manufacturing Company; Lowell Dress Manufacturing; Woonsocket Dress Company, Inc.
  - Berkshire Apparel, Inc. Pollack Brothers, 1965-1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Beverly Paige, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Biflex. Marion, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. General [folders 1-16 of 26], 1957-1979 (Box 15, Folder 7-22)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. General [folders 17-26 of 26], 1957-1979 (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Arbitration Cases and Proceedings, 1966-1979 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Cleveland Production Center, 1965-1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Contractors. [folder 1 of 4], 1964-1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Monthly Union Lists
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Contractors. [folder 2 of 4], 1964-1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Contractors. [folder 3 of 4], 1964-1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Contractors. [folder 4 of 4], 1964-1973 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Cost of Living, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Demands, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    Mostly 1973
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Labor Relations Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Master Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Master Agreements Summaries. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1976 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Master Agreements Summaries. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1976 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Master Agreements and Supplemental Agreements, 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Mediation Notices., 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 4 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 5 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 6 of 6], 1966-1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Union Label (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Undated.
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Addenda, 1969-1972 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Bellaire Garment Company, 1965-1978 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Butler Garment Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Cleveland Distribution Center, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Colebrook of Hialeah. [folder 1 of 5], 1964-1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Colebrook of Hialeah. [folder 2 of 5], 1964-1977 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Colebrook of Hialeah. [folder 3 of 5], 1964-1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Colebrook of Hialeah. [folder 4 of 5], 1964-1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Colebrook of Hialeah. [folder 5 of 5], 1964-1977 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Contract Garment Sewing Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Davis Knitting Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Deer Park Garment Company, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Dover Garment Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Erie Knitting Company, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Helena Garment Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Lepanto Garment Company, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Leslie Fay, Inc., 1972 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    Lincoln Supplemental
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Max Siegel and Associates, 1965-1971 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Memorandum of Understanding, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Regarding subsidiaries
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Middletown Garment Company, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Montgomery-Sylvania Manufacturing, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    Also joint contract with Lockhaven Garment Company.
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Nan Leslie. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Outer, Ltd., 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Payne Suit, 1974-1980 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Randi-Robert, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Robbie Rivers Suits, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Royal Apparel, Inc., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Shutterbug, Inc., 1969 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Stacy Ames. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Stacy Ames. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Stacy Ames. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Stretchini, 1965-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Tru-Gan, Mfg., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Vandalia Garment Company, 1965-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Bobbie Brooks, Inc. Subsidiary. Washington Garment Company, 1965-1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Boston Joint Board, 1969-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Bryn Mawr, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Budget Dress Corporation. [folder 1 of 3], 1956-1966 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Budget Dress Corporation. [folder 2 of 3], 1956-1966 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Budget Dress Corporation. [folder 3 of 3], 1956-1966 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - General. C, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Chatham; Coamo
  - Canadian Industry-Wide Bargaining, 1967-1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New Jersey, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Central States, 1966-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Charleston Garment Company, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Charmfit of Hollywood, Inc., 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cotton City Industries, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cotton City Industries, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Cotton City Industries, Inc. Arbitration, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Country Miss, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Country Miss, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Country Miss, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - General. D, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Dalton
  - Deena Lingerie, Inc., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Devon Apparel, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Dino Industries, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Dress Industry Award, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Dress Joint Council Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1978 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Dress Joint Council Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1978 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - General. E (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Undated. Edmos Corporation; Elizabeth Stewart; Exquisite Form Industries
  - Eastern Region, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Erin Dress Manufacturing Company, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Evan-Picone, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - General. F, 1965-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Fashion Capital; Fenway Coats, Inc.
  - Fairfield-Noble, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Fanfare, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Federal Corset Company, Inc., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Galapago. The Villager, Inc., 1969 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Genesco (includes photographs), 1965-1972 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Genesco. M and S Ladies Tailors, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - General Negotiations, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - General Negotiations. firms, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Girltown, Inc., 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Wm. Gluckin and Company, Inc., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - General. H, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Harwood Companies, Inc.; Heckler Manufacturing
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1972 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. C.M. Clothing Company, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. Glasgow Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1970 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Handmacher-Vogel, Inc. Glasgow Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1970 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Harwood Manufacturing Company, 1969-1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Hazantown, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Infants', Children's and Sportswear Association, Inc., 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Jane And Linda Sportswear Company, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Jerry Silverman, Inc., 1970 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Jodi Fashions, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Jonathan Logan. General. [folders 1-6 of 12], 1949-1978 (Box 19, Folder 30-35)
  - Jonathan Logan. General. [folders 7-12 of 12], 1949-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
  - Jonathan Logan. Contract Demands, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jonathan Logan. Cost-of-living, 1970-1976 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Jonathan Logan. Credit Report, Contract Rates, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Jonathan Logan. General Survey of Selected Shops, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Reports of 14 shops - plant surveys
  - Jonathan Logan. Master Agreements, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Jonathan Logan. Master Agreement Supplements, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Jonathan Logan. Master Agreement Transportation Supplements, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Jonathan Logan. Mediation Notices, 1969-1972 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Jonathan Logan. Memorandum of Agreement, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Jonathan Logan. Negotiations., 1964-1975 (Box 20, Folder 16-23)
    includes Piece Work Averages in files 22 and 23
  - Jonathan Logan. Negotiations. Canada. [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Jonathan Logan. Negotiations. Canada. [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Jonathan Logan. Negotiations. Canada. [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1968 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Jonathan Logan. Negotiation Demands, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Jonathan Logan. Supplementary Unemployment Severance Benefits Fund, ILGWU, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    mostly Benefits Applications
  - Jonathan Logan. Transportation Letter Agreement, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Jonathan Logan. Affiliates and Division Subsidiaries. Master Agreement, 1969-1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Act III, 1964-1967 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Alix of Hialeah, 1966-1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Alix of Miami, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Andrew Knitting, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 10a)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Aryea Dress Company, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Belmont Manufacturing Company, 1964-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Bennington Manufacturing Company, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Brookfield Mills of Sanford, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills, 1964-1979 (Box 21, Folder 15-23)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills, Act III, Modern Juniors Demands, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Grievances. [folder 1 of 2], 1969- 1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Grievances. [folder 2 of 2], 1969- 1972 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Letter Agreement, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1967- 1974 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1967- 1974 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1966- 1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    Negotiations - work sheets
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1966- 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Pay Schedules, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Piece Rates and Cost Calculations. [folder 1 of 4], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Piece Rates and Cost Calculations. [folder 2 of 4], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Piece Rates and Cost Calculations. [folder 3 of 4], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Piece Rates and Cost Calculations. [folder 4 of 4], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Supplemental Agreements. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Supplemental Agreements. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1972 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Butte Knitting Mills. Wage Increases, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Calhoun Manufacturing, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Cara and Morris Manufacturing, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Caribe Harbour. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Caribe Harbour. [folder 2 of 2], 1965-1972 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Century Sportswear, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Clinton Sportswear, 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Davis Sportswear Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1964- 1970 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Davis Sportswear Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1964- 1970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Debra Fashions, 1968-1972 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Donnefeld Knitting Mills, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. E.J. Sportswear, 1966-1971 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Fulton Knit, Inc., 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Gaffney-Maid Manufacturing Company, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Greene Manufacturing Company, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. The Immerman Corporation, 1955-1968 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Kim Fashions, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Kingston Dresses, Inc., 1964-1966 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. The Kramer Company, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Lawrence Manufacturing Company, 1964-1972 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Margaret Fashions, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Mercer Dress, 1963-1972 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Minotola Operating Corporation, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 5], 1965- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 5], 1965- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. [folder 3 of 5], 1965- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. [folder 4 of 5], 1965- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. [folder 5 of 5], 1965- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. Negotiations, 1970- 1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Misty Harbour Manufacturing Company. Progressions, 1969- 1975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Modern Juniors, Inc., 1966-1970 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Morris Manufacturing Company, 1964-1970 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    includes Collective Agreement National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc. with ILGWU and Dressmakers Joint Council
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Oxford Fashions, 1966-1976 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Spartan Undies, 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Spartan Undies. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1965- 1970 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Spartan Undies. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1965- 1970 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Steven Fashions, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Thomson Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Transportation Division, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Turtle Bay, Inc., 1965-1969 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Upper South Department, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Washmore Frocks, Inc., 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jonathan Logan. Subsidiaries and Affiliates. Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    Management Engineering Department - Plants Study
  - Josanna Coat Company, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Judy Bond, Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - General. K, 1968-1977 (Box 23, Folder 32)